

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a proactive person, an excellent team player, organized, and responsible. I greatly enjoy learning new things, so my goal is to find a challenging and dynamic position where I can share my experience and, at the same time, gain new knowledge.

#### CONTACT

Phone: (55) 18086702

Email: manuel.gallardo@lasallistas.org.mx

## **SKILLS**

#### Technical

HTML // CSS // JavaScript (Basic)

#### Design

 User research // wireframing// Usability studies // Prototyping

### Soft Skills

 Teamwork // commnunication // problem solving

### **LANGUAGES**

English - B2

### **PORTFOLIO**

https://manugallard.github.io/ Portafolio/index.html

# Manuel Gallardo

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY



# **EXPERIENCE**

## **Administrative Manager**

GEMCOMM COMUNICACIONES SA DE CV, JAN 2019 - SEPT 2023

- Management and coordination of an internal system to improve sales, after-sales, collection, customer service, and billing processes effectively.
- Prepared detailed quotations for clients, ensuring a clear presentation of products and services.
- Maintained proactive tracking of customer status, providing high-quality service and resolving any issues or concerns effectively.
- Supervised the sales cycle from lead identification to successful conclusion, ensuring a smooth and satisfactory experience for clients.
- Conducted detailed analysis of employee performance, generating reports highlighting sales and appointments made, identifying areas for improvement, and proposing effective solutions.

#### **Administrative Assistant**

PÉREZ Y ASOCIADOS, AUG 2016 - JAN 2017

• Expedite tracking, attendance at trials, and procedures with various agencies.



## **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021 Information Technology
Universidad La Salle

2022 **Diploma in Web Application** 

**Development with Python and Django** 

Universidad Anáhuac Mérida

2023 UX Design Certificate

Google - Coursera